https://kernwheelmen.org/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy applies to the use of kernwheelmen.org.
We highly value your privacy and make this policy easily available throughout our site to assist you in understanding the handling of information in the course of using this site.
Log Files and Cookies
This website utilizes industry standard analytics packages which gathers limited information on visitors to our website automatically, and stores this anonymous information in server log files. This information may include IP addresses, browser type, basic IP information, referring pages, operating system used and date/time stamps. This information does not identify individual users; it is used only for site administration, as well as for analysis of website usage and trends.
Additionally, cookies may be used to provide easier and faster access to website features such as logins and/or repeat visits. Cookies are very small text files that are stored on personal computers for reference purposes.
We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie expires when your browser is closed, and a persistent cookie may stay on your hard drive for an extended period. Session cookies make it easier for you to navigate our site; persistent cookies can perform such activities as maintaining your authenticated status so you do not have to sign in every time you visit.
We have no access to or administration abilities over any cookies that are used by any advertisers on our site.
Registration and Use of Personal Information
Registration is not required in order to use or access this website. However, there are many features that do require you to register, such as publishing your own data and comments.
If you do register, and in the process provide us with personally identifiable information, rest assured that any such information you provide will not be shared with any third-party organization except with your express consent.
Please note that if you publish data or comments to this site, any personally identifiable information you provide in those comments or articles may be read, collated and used by anyone viewing them. As such, we are not responsible for personally identifiable information you may choose to make available through these channels.
We also provide visitors to our website the opportunity to opt-in to receive communications from us. These communications will include any information that we feel may be pertinent to the visitor. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications by logging in to your account and navigating to the “Edit my profile” page.
Again, if you provide us with your email address and/or name for the purposes of receiving communications from us, this information will not be shared with any third-party organization except with your express consent.
Security
We follow accepted industry standards to protect any personal information you have provided to us. However, please be aware that no method of electronic storage can ever be 100% secure. Therefore as is the case with any organization – we are not in a position to guarantee the absolute security of your information.
You may submit any questions you may have about our security procedures by emailing us at ridewithgps@gmail.com.
Links to Other Websites
This website may contain links to other sites that are not controlled in any way by us. Please be aware of this when you click on any such links; we are not responsible for the privacy practices and/or policies of any website other than our own. Consequently, we strongly suggest that you review the privacy policy of every website you visit, whether or not they are linked to by our own site.
Legal Disclaimer
We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order or legal process served on our website.
Contact Details
If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, or you wish to contact us, our contact information is as follows:
president@kernwheelmen.org
This privacy policy was last updated on March 24, 2016.
Keep in touch
Fill in your details and we’ll get back to you in no time.
Fill in your details and we’ll get back to you in no time.
Keep in touch
Fill in your details and we’ll get back to you in no time.
Keep in touch
Fill in your details and we’ll get back to you in no time.
Keep in touch
Fill in your details and we’ll get back to you in no time.
Keep in touch
Fill in your details and we’ll get back to you in no time.
Keep in touch
Fill in your details and we’ll get back to you in no time.
